Viewers all over the world,
there are certain things in your life that, if not restored, you cannot be happy.
Right now, viewers all over the world,
whatever is required to make you happy - be restored!
Be restored!
[Touch the screen by faith and receive]
Viewers, wherever you are, whatever position you are in - are you sick?
Are you in-between decisions?
Are you at the point of death?
Whatever is required to make you happy - be restored!
[Touch the screen by faith and receive]
Be restored!
Viewers, it may be your walking with the Lord, that is questionable.
You may even not know, except that you are not happy,
and people see you with money, children, wife
and a fine and good marriage.
You have a good marriage, house - everything is good,
and yet you are not happy.
And only you know that you are not happy.
Out there, they want you to be their role model.
Yet, you - their mentor, are not happy.
Only you know that you are not happy.
Whatever is required to make you happy - be restored, in the name of Jesus!
Be restored, in the name of Jesus!
Your job - be restored!
Your health - be restored!
Your marriage - be restored!
Your business - be restored!
Your finances - be restored!
[Touch the Screen by Faith and Receive]
Your walking with the Lord - be restored!
In Jesus Christ's name, we pray!
[Touch the Screen by Faith and Receive]